A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
The Library of Virginia
31048, 31216, 43207, 43865, 44420, 45267, 50877, 51054, 51212, 51525
212 cu. ft.
Virginia Community College System. Chancellor.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and is restricted from public access for 75 years. These files are open for access, but files may contain confidential education records or other protected information that must be restricted (see Code of Virginia 2.2-3705.4 and 2.2-3801). It will be necessary for an archivist to review unprocessed material for confidential education or other information for removal or redaction before files can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of records can be made for patrons.
Acquisition Information
Virginia Community College System Offices, Chancellor's Office, 101 N. 14th Street, Richmond, VA 23219. Accession 31048 transferred 16 December 1980. Accession 31216 transferred 16 July 1981. Accession 43207 transferred 8 May 2007. Accession 43865 transferred 7 July 2008. Accession 44420 transferred 29 July 2009. Accession 45267 transferred 19 November 2010. Accession 50877 transferred 22 April 2013. Accession 51054 transferred 27 September 2013. Accession 51212 transferred 21 February 2014. Accession 51525 transferred 8 April 2015.
Scope and Content
These records consist of the correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System. These records document academic, personnel, fiscal and administrative activities, policies and procedures. Includes correspondence with community colleges and their presidents, as well as state and federal agencies; topical files; and committee meeting records and minutes.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1973-1978 [Accession 31048]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1980 [Accession 31216]
Series III: Correspondence and subject files, 1990-2003 [Accession 43207]
Series V: Correspondence and subject files, 1964-1997 [Accession 44420]
Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, 1969-2008 [Accession 45267]
Series VII: Correspondence and subject files, 1988-2005 [Accession 50877]
Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 51054]
Series IX: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 51212]
Series X: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 51525]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31048], 1973-1978., Extent: 34 cu. ft. (34 boxes). (Box 1-34)
  - Subseries A. 1973-1976
    - "A" Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - ADP Task Force report (Box 1)
    - AACJC (Box 1)
    - AAUP (Box 1)
    - AAUP (Box 1)
    - American Association of University Professors Bulletin (Box 1)
    - AAUP Publications (Box 1)
    - ADP Committee meeting (Box 1)
    - AAUP Censure of VCCS (Box 1)
    - Academic Calendar (Box 1)
    - Accounting (Box 1)
    - Adult Basic, General, Continuing Technical and Vocational Education (Box 1)
    - Adult Education, Joint Committee, HJR No. 137 (Box 1)
    - Advisory group of scholars of the Chamber of Commerce (Box 1)
    - Administration, Secretary of (Box 1)
    - Administration and Finance (Box 1)
    - Advertising policy (Box 1)
    - Affirmative Action activities, Semi-Annual report (Box 1)
    - Administration and Finance monthly reports (Box 1)
    - Administrative Officers in VCCS (Box 1)
    - Admissions requirements, Task Force (Box 1)
    - Administration and Finance, Reports, documents, etc. (Box 2)
    - Aerospace Education Foundation (Box 2)
    - Aeronautics, Division of (Box 2)
    - Affirmative Action Plan (Box 2)
    - The Alfalfa Club (Box 2)
    - American Association of Bible Colleges (Box 2)
    - Applications (Box 2)
    - Appropriation Act (Box 2)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 2)
    - Architects fees and projects (Box 2)
    - Architects and Engineers (Box 2)
    - Armed Forces, Community Colleges programs in conjunction with (Box 2)
    - Army, Dept. of (Box 2)
    - U.S. Army Transportation School (Box 2)
    - The Art Commission (Box 2)
    - Arts and Humanities, Commission of (Box 2)
    - ASAP (Box 2)
    - Ashland College (Box 2)
    - Assessment Center (Box 2)
    - Articulation (Box 2)
    - Association for Biological Education (Box 2)
    - Association of Community College Trustees (Box 2)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 2)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 2)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges (Box 2)
    - Armistead, Blenda Woodard (Box 2)
    - American Association for Higher Education (Box 2)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (Box 2)
    - Agricultural Council Meeting (Box 2)
    - Agriculture (Box 2)
    - Appointment proposal forms (Box 2)
    - Audit, Travel account (Box 2)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 2)
    - Appalachian Regional Committee (Box 2)
    - Appendix "M" Subcommittee for Budget (Box 2)
    - Agricultural Education Task Force (Box 3)
    - Agriculture and Commerce (Box 3)
    - Aging, Virginia Office of the (Box 3)
    - Airlines (Box 3)
    - American Dental Association (Box 3)
    - American Vocational Association (Box 3)
    - American Management Association (Box 3)
    - American Council on Education (Box 3)
    - American Council on Education (Box 3)
    - American Council on Education, Publications (Box 3)
    - Annual reports (Box 3)
    - Annual reports (Box 3)
    - Annual meetings (Box 3)
    - Apiculture (Box 3)
    - Assistant Attorney General (Box 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 3)
    - Averett College (Box 3)
    - Attorney General's Office State Agency (Box 3)
    - Attorney General's Conference on College Law (Box 3)
    - Assistant Attorney General for Dept. (Box 3)
    - Audio Visual (Box 3)
    - ADP Master Plan (Box 3)
    - Air Force, Community College (Box 3)
    - Automate Date Processing, ADP Meeting (Box 3)
    - Benefits for employees (Box 4)
    - Budget (Box 4)
    - Budget (Box 4)
    - Cagle, Vice Admiral Malcolm W. (Box 4)
    - CASE (Council for Advancement and Support of Education) (Box 4)
    - Central Richmond Association (Box 4)
    - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education (Box 4)
    - Central Va. Educational TV (Box 4)
    - Certified Professional Secretary (Box 4)
    - Certified Professional Secretary (Box 4)
    - Certified Public Secretary (Box 4)
    - Catholic University (Box 4)
    - College Law Conference (Box 4)
    - Commencement (Box 4)
    - The Commission on Colleges (Box 4)
    - Commission on Status of Women (Box 4)
    - Commonwealth, Secretary of (Box 4)
    - Community College Review, Publications (Box 4)
    - Community College Review (Box 4)
    - Community College Editorial Board Meeting (Washington, DC) (Box 4)
    - Community Colleges of Va. Educational Foundation, Inc. Meeting (Williamsburg, Va.) (Box 4)
    - Comptroller, State (Box 4)
    - Community and Junior College Journal (Box 4)
    - Congress (Box 4)
    - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of (Box 4)
    - Consolidated Salary Authorization (Box 4)
    - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education, Tidewater (Box 4)
    - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education, Western Va. (Box 4)
    - Construction Progress Report (Box 4)
    - Construction, Public Works Employment Act Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Consultants (Box 4)
    - Consumer Information (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service (Box 4)
    - Copyrighting (Box 4)
    - Corrections, Dept. of (Box 4)
    - Costello, Mrs. W. R. (Box 4)
    - Council of Visitors Committee (Box 4)
    - California Community and Junior College Association (Box 5)
    - Campus Police Legislation (Box 5)
    - Cape Fear Technical Institute (Box 5)
    - Capital Consortium (Box 5)
    - Capital Outlay Projects, Funded (Box 5)
    - Capital Outlay Coordinating Committee for Higher Education (Box 5)
    - Council of Presidents (Four-Year Colleges) (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Guide, State (Box 5)
    - D, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Dental Continuing Education Committee (Box 5)
    - Developmental Studies (Box 5)
    - Directors Itinerary (Box 5)
    - E, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School Bulletin (Box 5)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical Authority (Box 5)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 5)
    - Enrollments Booklet (Box 5)
    - Enrollment, Budget and Actual Projected (Box 5)
    - Enrollments, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Enrollment Projections (Box 5)
    - Enrollments (Box 5)
    - Educational Programs, Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories (Box 5)
    - Educational Programs Division (Box 5)
    - EDUCOM, Educational Communications (Box 5)
    - Elder, Mrs. Anne (Box 5)
    - Emergency Services, Office of (Box 5)
    - Energy Office, State (Box 5)
    - Engineering and Building (Box 5)
    - Erosion and Sediment Control Committee (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5)
    - F, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Federal Funds (Box 5)
    - Financial Statements (Box 5)
    - General Assembly (Box 5)
    - Graham, Billy, Bicentennial Festival of Faith (Box 5)
    - H, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - I, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Isothermal Community College (Box 5)
    - Independent Colleges in Virginia, Council of (Box 6)
    - Industrial Development, Division of (Box 6)
    - Institutions, Out of State (Box 6)
    - Insurance, General (Box 6)
    - Invoices (Box 6)
    - Invoices (Box 6)
    - JLARC (Box 6)
    - K, Miscellaneous (Box 6)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 6)
    - School Law Newsletter (Box 6)
    - Legal matters (Box 6)
    - Legislative Services, Division of (Box 6)
    - Letterhead - Stationery for system (Box 6)
    - Longwood College (Box 6)
    - McManis Associates, Consultants (Box 6)
    - Management by Objective (Box 6)
    - Management by Objective (Box 6)
    - Management by Objective (Box 6)
    - Management Information System (Box 6)
    - Management Information System (Box 6)
    - Martinez, Mr. Paul C. (Box 6)
    - Management by Objective, Manual (Box 7)
    - Master Plan, Community Colleges of Virginia (Box 7)
    - Materials for Legal Assistant (Box 7)
    - Meeting facilities (Box 7)
    - Membership (Box 7)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Box 7)
    - N, Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - National Council of State Directors (Box 7)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 7)
    - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (Box 7)
    - National Council of State Directors (Box 7)
    - National Guard, Va. and other recruiting programs, etc. (Box 7)
    - Network Trainers (Box 7)
    - News Releases (Box 7)
    - North Carolina, University of (Box 7)
    - Norfolk State College (Box 7)
    - North Carolina State College (Box 7)
    - Numbering system (Box 7)
    - Nursing licensure (Box 7)
    - Nursing (Box 7)
    - OMNI Hotel (Box 7)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 7)
    - Office equipment (Box 7)
    - Overtime (Box 7)
    - P, Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Parking (Box 7)
    - Payroll Supervisor (Box 7)
    - Personnel, Division of (Box 7)
    - Personnel Committee, Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Philip Morris (Box 7)
    - Planning and Community Affairs (Box 7)
    - Planning Districts (Box 7)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 7)
    - Post secondary Personnel Development publications (Box 7)
    - Policy manual (Box 8)
    - Policies and procedures (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Research and Information Committee, Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 8)
    - Finance Committee, Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Presidents Advisory Council (Box 8)
    - Printing and duplicating (Box 8)
    - Policy Public Office, Community College (Box 8)
    - Printing request forms (Box 8)
    - Private Colleges (Box 8)
    - Privacy Act of 1976 (Box 8)
    - Professional Employees Appointment Policy Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Project Ahead (Box 8)
    - Psychological Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
    - Publications Act (Box 8)
    - Property Records and Insurance, Dept. of (Box 8)
    - Publications (Box 8)
    - Purchasing section (Box 8)
    - Purchases and Supplies, Dept. of (Box 8)
    - Purchase requisition (Box 8)
    - Questionnaires, surveys, etc. (Box 8)
    - Questionnaires, surveys, etc. (Box 8)
    - R, Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Radford College (Box 9)
    - Rehabilitative School Authority (Box 9)
    - Research and Planning (Box 9)
    - Richmond Eye Hospital (Box 9)
    - Regrets (Box 9)
    - Resolutions (Box 9)
    - Salaries (Box 9)
    - Salary Schedule for Faculty (Box 9)
    - Salary information (Box 9)
    - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits (Box 9)
    - SCATS (Box 9)
    - Savings Bond Drive (Box 9)
    - SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education of Virginia), Health Professions and Occupations (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, College budget submissions (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, Advisory Committees (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee) (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, ADP Committee (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, Appropriations (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, ADP Master Plan (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, ADP (Box 9)
    - SCHEV, Pilot study (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Post Secondary Education Research (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Research and Development Advisory Committee (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Space Utilization report (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Va. Information Exchange Procedure Documentation (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Time and attendance record (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Council notes (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Council notes (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, FIPSE Advisory Committee (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Instructional Programs Advisory Committee (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Inventory of Post secondary Education (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Task Force on continuing Health Education (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Paramedical Personnel Studies Committee (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Instructional Programs Advisory Committee (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, State Aid to Private Higher Education in Virginia (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, News releases and council notes (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Programs approved (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - SCHEV, Workshop (Box 10)
    - SACS (Southern Association of Colleges and Schools), Presidency Correspondence (Box 10)
    - SACS, Presidency Correspondence (Box 10)
    - SACS, Presidency Correspondence (Box 10)
    - SACS, Standards (Box 10)
    - SACS, Proceedings (Box 11)
    - SACS, Presidency, Executive Committee (Box 11)
    - SACS, Personnel Committee Meetings (Box 11)
    - SACS Meeting (Atlanta, Ga.) (Box 11)
    - SACS Meeting (Atlanta, Ga.) (Box 11)
    - SACS, Policies and Procedures of the Commission on Colleges (Box 11)
    - Southern Regional Educational Board (Box 11)
    - Southern Regional Educational Board, Publications (Box 11)
    - Scott, Gail P., Resume (Box 11)
    - Scott, Roland (Box 11)
    - The Scottish Rite News (Box 11)
    - Senate Bill 315 (Box 11)
    - Significant issues (Box 11)
    - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety (Box 11)
    - Special Training Division Guidelines (Box 11)
    - Snyder, Dr. Fred (Box 11)
    - Speakers information (Box 11)
    - Special Programs, Office of (Box 11)
    - SCHEV, General Professional Advisory Committee (Box 11)
    - Special Committee to study relationships between committees on colleges and SACS (Box 11)
    - SRA and SCAT Test scores (Box 11)
    - State Fair (Box 11)
    - Stationary, Community College (Box 11)
    - Student Aid (Box 11)
    - Student Data (Box 11)
    - Student numbers (Box 11)
    - Student classification seminar (Box 11)
    - Success story file (Box 12)
    - Sullins College (Box 12)
    - Supplemental retirement system (Box 12)
    - Surveying (Box 12)
    - Sweet, Charles V. (Box 12)
    - Tarrant County Junior College District (Box 12)
    - Teaching load (Box 12)
    - Telecommunications Council (Box 12)
    - Temple, Edward T. (Box 12)
    - Tidewater Area Health Education Subcommittee meeting (Box 12)
    - U, Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - United Givers Fund (Box 12)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 12)
    - V, Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - VCU Nursing (Box 12)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 12)
    - Virginia Education Association (Box 12)
    - Virginia Education Association, Publications (Box 12)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (Box 12)
    - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities (Box 12)
    - Virginia Regional Medical Program (Box 12)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 12)
    - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, Inc. (Box 12)
    - VPI New Horizon Conference (Box 12)
    - Various Community College, MBO (Management by Objectives) Plans (Box 12)
    - W, Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - The William Oncken Company (Box 12)
    - William and Mary (Box 12)
    - Word processing (Box 12)
    - Wright, Marcellus (Box 12)
    - Xerox Education Center (Box 12)
  - Subseries B. 1977
    - A, Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - AACJC (Community and Junior College Journal) (Box 13)
    - AACJC, Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - AACJC Meeting (Denver, Co.) (Box 13)
    - ADP (Box 13)
    - ADP Policy Committee (Box 13)
    - ADP Resource Sharing Task force (Box 13)
    - American Association of University Professors Bulletin (Box 13)
    - AAUP (Box 13)
    - Academic and Student Affairs (Box 13)
    - Academic and Student Affairs (Box 13)
    - Accounting (Box 13)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 13)
    - ACCtion Consortium (Box 13)
    - Administration building, VCCS (Box 13)
    - Administration, Dean of (Box 13)
    - Administrative's Assistant's Office (Box 13)
    - Administrative Officers in VCCS (Box 13)
    - Advisory Committee, VCCCS (Box 13)
    - Advisory Council for Educational Computing (ACEC) (Box 13)
    - Aeronautics, Division of (Box 13)
    - Aerospace Education Foundation (Box 13)
    - Aerospace Education Foundation (Box 13)
    - Aerospace Education Foundation, Meeting (Washington, D.C.) (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action Committee (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action Committee (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action Evaluation survey (Box 13)
    - Aging, Virginia Office of (Box 13)
    - Agribusiness Council (Box 13)
    - Agriculture, Commission of the Industry (Box 13)
    - Agriculture and Commerce (Box 13)
    - Agricultural Education, Task Force for (Box 13)
    - Agriculture, Film Script Publication (Box 13)
    - Air Force Association (Box 13)
    - Alcohol Safety Action Project (Box 14)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (Box 14)
    - American Association for Higher Education, Publications (Box 14)
    - American Council on Education Board (Box 14)
    - American Council on Education Board (Box 14)
    - American Council on Education Board, Meeting (Washington, DC) (Box 14)
    - American Council on Education Board (Chicago, IL) (Box 14)
    - American Council on Education, Publications (Box 14)
    - American Institutes for Research in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 14)
    - American Management Association (Box 14)
    - American Society of Public Administration, Va. Chapter (Box 14)
    - American Vocational Association (Box 14)
    - Annual meeting, Invitations to College Boards (Box 14)
    - Annual report and meeting (Box 14)
    - Annual report (Box 14)
    - Apiculture (Box 14)
    - Apiculture Committee (Box 14)
    - Appalachia, Publications (Box 14)
    - Appalachian Regional Committee (Box 14)
    - Applicants (Box 14)
    - Applicants, Classified (Box 14)
    - Applications, Faculty (Box 14)
    - Appointment contracts (Box 14)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 14)
    - Architects and engineers (Box 14)
    - Articulation agreements (Box 14)
    - Articulation, Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Arts and Humanities, Commission of (Box 14)
    - Ashland College (Box 14)
    - Association of Community College Trustees (Box 14)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 14)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges (Box 14)
    - Assistant Attorney General's Office (Box 14)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 14)
    - Averett College (Box 14)
    - Audit Section (Box 14)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 14)
    - Audio Visual (Box 14)
    - Awards conferred (Box 14)
    - B, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Bank of Virginia (Box 15)
    - Battelle, Workshop, Educational Management (Box 15)
    - Bender, Lou (Box 15)
    - Board Room schedule (Box 15)
    - Boards, Statutory Grants of Power Task Force (SJR 96) (Box 15)
    - Bond issue (Box 15)
    - Bottled Gas Corporation of Virga (Box 15)
    - Boushall, Thomas C. (Box 15)
    - Budgets, Division of (Box 15)
    - Budget coordinator, Boynton, Douglas T. (Box 15)
    - Budget Office (Box 15)
    - Budget Affairs and Planning (Box 15)
    - Budget Office, Expenditure Reduction Impact Statements (Box 15)
    - Budget (Box 15)
    - Budget manual (Box 15)
    - Budget (Box 15)
    - Budget, Statement of financial condition (Box 15)
    - Budget, Statement Department (Box 15)
    - Budget Workshops (Box 15)
    - Business Industry surveys (Box 15)
    - Byrd, Harry F., Jr. (Box 15)
    - C, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - CB Report, Publications (Box 15)
    - Calendar correspondence (Box 15)
    - Calendar project (Box 15)
    - Calendar of events (Box 15)
    - Calendar, Review of Public (Box 15)
    - California Community and Junior College Association (Box 15)
    - Capital Consortium (Box 15)
    - Capital Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay request (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay, Funded projects (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay Tour (Box 15)
    - Capital Outlay Biennium Priority Groups (Box 15)
    - Cars, Regulations and Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 15)
    - Cars, Dr. Hamel's (Box 15)
    - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education (Box 15)
    - Carter, Robert (Box 15)
    - Catalog (Box 15)
    - CenTex, Board of Directors' Meetings (Box 15)
    - CenTex, Board of Directors' Meetings (Box 15)
    - CenTex, Center of Excellence (Box 15)
    - Central garage Car Pool Services (Box 15)
    - Certification of Teachers (Box 15)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Va. (Box 15)
    - Chamber of Commerce, US (Box 15)
    - Chancellors memos (Box 16)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee (Box 16)
    - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, Executive Committee Members (Box 16)
    - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, Curriculum and Program Committee (Box 16)
    - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, Building and Site Committee (Box 16)
    - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, Budget and Finance Committee (Box 16)
    - Memos to Deputy Chancellors from Chancellor (Box 16)
    - Change, Publication (Box 16)
    - Chart Presentation, Virginia Community College System (Box 16)
    - Chart Presentation, Virginia Community College System (Box 16)
    - Chart of accounts (Box 16)
    - Charter Day (Box 16)